virtualphotographystudio.com 2008-09-19

# Virtual Photography Studio - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**We value your privacy!**

We operate under the following strict privacy policy: 

The only information we obtain about you is information you provide when signing up for our reports, ezines, or purchase products and/or services. The information collected is never revealed, sold, or made public for any reason. Personally identifiable information provided (name, email or home address, etc.) is never disclosed to any individual or business. 

VirtualPhotographyStudio.com is committed to maintaining the trust of our users. This statement explains how we collect information from you and what we do with the information.

VirtualPhotographyStudio.com is solely focused on providing entrepreneurs with the high quality, ethical tools and information they need to market their small businesses. None of the information or tools provided on the VirtualPhotographyStudio.com web site is intended for unethical or illegal marketing practices, including but not limited to:

**Private Forums**

We provide our visitors with access to our Discussion Forum that makes sharing information with other members easy. To protect your privacy when posting or replying to messages in the message board, your personal information and email is not revealed. However, remember that any information you disclose in the message board areas can be read by all other members, so exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Opt-In and Information Requests:**

VirtualPhotographyStudio.com offers a variety of on-line resources. To make full use of the resource on our site, we ask you to provide some basic information. Our site gives users the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. You can be assured that we never reveal, sell, or make available your email address to anyone for any purpose. This site also gives users options for removing their information from our database in order to stop receiving our communications.

**Third Party Links**

Occasionally we may provide links to various third party websites. We do this to provide you with a greater value, and create a better experience for your business. We never share your information with these third party sites. However, once you leave our site, third party websites operate under their own privacy policy. Tracking, cookies and information gathering is solely at their discretion. 

**Contact Information:**

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by e-mail at [info@VirtualPhotographyStudio.com](mailto:info@VirtualPhotographyStudio.com)

**Changes to this Policy**

VirtualPhotographyStudio.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

**Governing law**

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Colorado law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Denver, Colorado. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: Denver, Colorado, under the rules of the American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
